# Meghan Pitsch

226 E. Bridge St. Rockford, MI | (616)540-4437 | Meghan.pitsch@gmail.com

# **Personal Profile**

I am a hardworking, responsible, and open minded individual possessing excellent communication and time management skills. I have a unique employment background which blends extensive experience in customer service with a passion for community service and international affairs.

# **Experience**

WORKSHOP SPECIALIST | GOODWILL INDUSTRIES OF GREATER GRAND RAPIDS | PRESENT

INTERN AND VOLUNTEER | WORLD AFFAIRS COUNCIL | 2015-PRESENT

MANAGER AND CONCIERGE DIRECTOR | CELEBRATION! CINEMA | 2011-2017

INTERN TO CHIEF JUDGE | KALAMAZOO COUNTY PROBATE COURT | 2014-2015

CORPS MEMBER | AMERICORPS NCCC | 2010-2011

## **Skills & Abilities**

#### MANAGEMENT AND ORGANIZATIONAL LEADERSHIP

- · Supervised staff of 100+ in day to day duties of operating a movie theater
- Entered and approved employee work hours for payroll
- · Co-supervised and coordinated volunteer efforts in initial relief of Joplin Tornado Disaster

#### **CUSTOMER SERVICE**

- Utilized problem solving skills to handle customer concerns and emergency situations
- Trained and supervised Concierge staff who deliver superior service for up to 8000 guests per day
- · Received four awards for Superior Customer Service at Celebration! Cinema

#### **COMMUNICATION**

- · Instructed job skills workshops for participants in Goodwill's Achieve program
- · Managed content on World Affairs Council of West Michigan website
- · Member of Toastmasters International

#### TIME MANAGEMENT

- · Completion of Juvenile Mental Health Court Grant Proposal as Probate Court Intern
- · Able to coordinate both short term and long term deadlines successfully
- · Certified as Goodwill Instructor while providing support services to Goodwill's CNA program

### **Education**

B.A. GLOBAL AND INTERNATIONAL STUDIES | 2016 | WESTERN MICHIGAN UNIVERSITY